federalsoup.com 2018-10-11

# 1105 Media Privacy Policy -- 1105 Media

_**Effective May 1, 2018**_

**Our Approach to Privacy**  
1105 Media considers itself a steward of the information it collects, maintains and utilizes. Our responsibility is to ensure the security of the information in our care and to maintain the privacy of our data through appropriate, responsible use.

Today, our business clients' needs and expectations are constantly changing, and technology is constantly evolving. 1105 Media strives to constantly evolve with these changing needs and expectations to provide the most appropriate processes and policies in a timely manner.

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at **[privacy@1105media.com](mailto:privacy@1105media.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)** **and include 'Privacy Policy' in the subject line.**

1105 Media, LLC, its affiliates and its subsidiaries (collectively, **"1105 Media"** , **"us"** or **"we"** ) owns, operates, or provides access to, several interactive websites, online interactive features and services, including, but not limited to, emails, newsletters, chat areas, forums, communities. This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected about you by 1105 Media, regardless of how it is collected or stored, and describes, among other things, the types of information collected about you when you visit the Services, how your information may be used and when it may be disclosed, how you can control the use and disclosure of your information, and how your information is protected.

This Privacy Policy covers information collected through these websites:

### Privacy Policy Overview

In this Privacy Policy, we will discuss the following topics and more: 

  1. **What information we collect.**
  2. **How we collect and use information.**
  3. **Information regarding interest-based advertising.**
  4. **What information we share with third parties.**
  5. **How you can change or control what is collected.**
  6. **Information for users located outside the U.S.**
  7. **How this Privacy Policy can change.**
  8. **Other useful information regarding your privacy.**
  9. **Enforcement.**

#### 1\. What information we collect.

We may collect Personal Information from you or from other sources. **"Personal Information"** generally means information that might reasonably be used to specifically identify you and may include information such as:

  * Contact information, such as your name, postal address, email address, phone number and/or mobile number;
  * Demographic information such as job and professional information, company information, education and work experience;
  * User name and password; and Location data that describes the precise geographic location of your device ( **"Precise Location Data"** ). 

We do not intentionally collect data such as financial information or data concerning racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs or trade union membership.

We also collect other kinds of information from you or other sources, which we refer to as **"Other Information"** in this Privacy Policy. The type of information we collect may change as technologies evolve. Other Information may include, but is not limited to, information such as:

  * Areas or topics of interest;
  * Content of messages or comments posted by you or other users (e.g., text, photos, videos, and links) to the Services, including on forums or content;
  * Browsing history, including the websites or other services you visited before and after visiting the Services;
  * Device type, settings and software used;
  * Advertising ID, which is a unique, user-resettable identification number for advertising associated with a device (e.g. iOS uses the Identifier for Advertising (or **"IDFA"** ) and Android uses Google Advertising ID);
  * Internet Protocol ( **"IP"** ) address, which is a unique string of numbers automatically assigned to your device whenever you access the Internet;
  * Log files, which may include IP addresses, browser type, ISP referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamps and/or clickstream data, including any clicks on customized links;
  * Web Beacons, which are electronic files that allow a website to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies;
  * Pixel Tags, also known as clear GIFs, beacons, spotlight tags or web bugs, are a method for passing information from the user's computer to a third party website;
  * Non-precise information about the approximate physical location (for example, at the city or zip code level) of a user's computer or device derived from the IP address of such computer or device ("GeoIP Data");
  * Local Shared Objects, such as Flash cookies, and Local Storage, such as HTML5;
  * Information collected through the use of cookies, eTags, JavaScript, pixel tags, device ID tracking, anonymous identifiers and other technologies, including information collected using such methods and technologies about (i) your visits to, and interaction and engagement with, the Services and ads on third party websites, applications, platforms and other media channels, and (ii) your interaction with emails including the content and ads (collectively, **"Online Data"** ).

We may also supplement the Personal Information and Other Information we collect from you with information from third parties, including third party affiliate network operators, referral sources, social networking sites or services (such as Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn), and commercially available or public sources (such as data brokers, data aggregators and public databases). If you use a third-party connection or log-in (such as Facebook Connect, Twitter, or Google+) to access the Services, create a membership or profile on any part of the Services, access our content or forward our content to another person, platform or service, we may also receive your user name, password or email address for those third-party services or other information available about you or collected from you on those services. This Privacy Policy does not cover the practices of third parties, including those that may disclose information to 1105 Media.

**All of the above information is referred to collectively as "User Information".**

Please note that 1105 Media is not responsible for the information you volunteer about yourself in the discussions in certain public areas of the site, such as forums, blogs, wikis, chat rooms, private messages, message boards or other publicly accessible interaction, or information that you choose to make public in your member profile or other areas that allow users to upload or post content. We discourage users from posting Personal Information in this fashion. You can change your publicly available information at any time via your profile page or to request removal of your Personal Information from these areas. Please see our section on **How you can change or control what is collected** in this Privacy Policy. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

#### 2\. How we collect and use information.

1105 Media collects information as described herein. All information is or may be used as described in this Privacy Policy.

We collect User Information across our Services, such as when you register for site membership or create a profile or account on any part of the Services; purchase a subscription, software license or product; sign up for emails, newsletters, bulletins, webinars or white papers; enter a sweepstakes, contest, competition or prize draw; receive promotional information by SMS text message; participate in surveys; perform search queries on the Services; send an email to us; or otherwise communicate with us. We also collect User Information about you offline through telephone or direct mail efforts or from customers, vendors, suppliers, third parties and publicly-available sources.

When you use the Services, we may combine Personal Information with Other Information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you and to improve the functionality of the Services and our ability to market or advertise to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. We may also combine information you have provided to us with information obtained from other sources such as social networks.

Personal Information is used to provide Services to you from 1105 Media or its partners, which includes, but is not limited to when: (i) we send emails or newsletters offering services or products to you, (ii) you post your personal testimonial alongside other endorsements, (iii) we display your personal reviews of products or services, or (iv) you search for other website members using information you may already know about that member such as username, full name or gamer profile and identify users matching that criteria. Personal Information may also be used to send you advertisements and promotions on the Services and on third party channels. Personal Information you provide to us is used in a way that is compatible with the Services and this Privacy Policy. Some of the Services use Personal Information of a registered user to "pre-populate" online forms that are displayed for the purpose of collecting additional information about you by the Services or on behalf of a third party.

If you choose to use our referral service to send an article to a contact or to invite a contact to become a member of a website, we will ask you for your contact's email address or allow you to import your contacts from your email account's address book. We will automatically send your contact a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. We may collect the username and password for the email account from which you wish to import your contacts and will only use that information for that purpose.

1105 Media and its partners use cookies and other tracking technologies to analyze trends, administer Services, track users' movements around the Services and on third party sites, devices and applications, and to gather demographic information about our user base. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on the Services. To manage Flash cookies, please click **[here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)**. Please see our **Cookie Policy** for more information, including a more in-depth explanation of what cookies are, the different types of cookies used on the Services, and how to change or delete them.

Tracking technologies on the Services may be deployed by 1105 Media and/or by our service providers or partners. Certain tracking technologies enable us to assign a unique identifier to you and relate information about your use of the Services to other information about you, including your User Information. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times and use such information along with offline and online information obtained from other sources (including from third parties), including, but not limited to, demographic information and updated contact information for the purposes of learning more about you so we can provide you with relevant content and advertising.

When you receive email messages or newsletters from us, we may use web beacons, customized links, clear GIFs or similar technologies to determine whether the email has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused email communications or other information, and/or aggregate with other data we collect for some or all of the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy.

We and our partners (including but not limited to e-commerce partners, affiliates, and analytics providers) may also use technologies such as pixel tags, e-tags, IP addresses, Local Shared Objects, Local Storage, Flash cookies and HTML5 to analyze trends; administer the Services; collect and store information such as user settings, anonymous browser identifiers and video viewing history; supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement; track users' location and movements around the Services; gather demographic information about our user base; and to improve our understanding of traffic on the Services, visitor behavior, and responses to promotional campaigns. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these third party companies on an individual and aggregated basis. For example, we may connect information about your IP address to known corporate or other information or User Information and use the associated information related to aggregate content preferences to assist in our efforts to market services to you or the originating corporation(s). Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing Local Storage. To manage Flash Local Shared Objects please click **[here](http://www.adobe.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html)**.

#### 3\. Information regarding interest-based advertising.

1105 Media and/or certain third parties collect information about you for online behavioral advertising (" **OBA** ") purposes in order for you to receive relevant interest-based advertising on the Services and on other websites, platforms and media channels. OBA is also referred to as interest-based advertising.

1105 Media displays ads on both the Services and on third party websites, applications, platforms and other media channels (collectively, " **Channels** "). We use Online Data as well as other User Information to send you OBA. For example, if you read an article about a particular subject on the Services, we may use cookies from a vendor to later serve you an advertisement for a particular product or service related to the viewed article. These third party vendors may connect information about pages you visit on the Services with information about pages you visit on other Channels and show you advertising based on this combined information. These advertisements may appear when you are visiting a different section of the Services or on another Channel. Likewise, third party vendors may serve you advertisements when you visit the Services based on your interaction with the Services and other Channels.

Online Data is aggregated with the other information and data we collect as described in this Privacy Policy and/or similar data collected by partners to create groups of users and certain general-interest categories or segments that we have inferred based on (a) demographic or interest data and GeoIP Data, (b) the pages you view and links you click when viewing an email or using the Services and those of our partners, and/or (c) the search terms you enter when using certain search services. We use this information to get a more accurate picture of audience interests in order to serve ads we believe are more relevant to your interests. We store page views, clicks and search terms used for ad personalization targeting separately from your Personal Information.

We may also sell or transfer Online Data to certain third parties such as advertisers who will use this data to serve ads that they believe are relevant to your interests, and who agree to maintain the confidentiality of this information. Some of these third parties may combine the Online Data with their own data about you to form a more detailed picture.

We engage third party providers to assist with the collection, storage and segmentation of Online Data and the providers are required to maintain the confidentiality of this information. We do not authorize such third party providers to collect Personal Information from our Services for their own purposes. Except as may be set forth elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, this Online Data is retained by 1105 Media for not more than 180 days after which it shall expire. However, the 180-day period may commence again if the same user subsequently visits or interacts with an ad, email, the Services or a Channel.

We may also engage third parties for the purpose of recognizing our users and delivering interest-based content and advertisements to them. We may share your User Information with our partners such as your name, postal address, email, or other identifier. Our partners may also: (i) collect information directly from your device, such as your IP address, device ID, advertising ID, and information about your browser or operating system; (ii) combine User Information about you received from 1105 Media with information about you from other sites or services; and (iii) place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

One of the ways in which we collect this information is through Tracking Technologies such as cookies and web beacons. A cookie is a small file downloaded on to a device when a user accesses certain websites. Cookies are useful because they allow us to recognize your device and provide you with a high level of service and relevant offers. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. For more information about our use of cookies and other Tracking Technologies, please visit our Cookie Policy.

#### 4\. What information we share with third parties.

1105 Media provides User Information to third party companies and contractors who work on our behalf to provide us with specialized services, such as email message deployment, email address validation, merge-purge (identifying and removing duplicate addresses), subscription fulfillment, customer support and service, research, statistical analysis, cross-device user tracking, data and website hosting, marketing, advertising, and other data and transaction processing. These companies work on our behalf, are authorized by 1105 Media to obtain only the information they need to deliver the service and are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information. We also engage third party service providers for the purpose of processing the sale of subscriptions, to fulfill your orders for product purchases, to honor your request to be removed from promotional mailings, to monitor, analyze and prevent fraudulent traffic or other suspicious activities on the Services or Channels, or other services. These service providers have access to or are provided with certain User Information (including credit card information) in order to provide us with the applicable service.

At times, we conduct contests, competitions, sweepstakes and prize draws, or produce and host sponsored white papers, webcasts or other downloads for a variety of companies ( **"Sponsors"** ). Information collected during the registration for such events is used by us as part of User Information and may be shared with the Sponsor and others. The information collected would be subject to our Privacy Policy and, in the event that it is shared with a Sponsor or other third party, would also be subject to the Sponsor's or such other third party's privacy policy, and it may be used by us, the Sponsor, and/or such other third parties for follow up purposes. We may also share your information with third party vendors involved in the administration of such events. For contests, competitions, sweepstakes and prize draws, please read the official rules or terms and conditions carefully before you submit your information.

For some of our Services, we may make some information, such as the name of our users, their mailing address, phone number, email address—and in certain circumstances their employer's name, company size and other industry data—available on a rental or other basis (e.g. sale) to third party providers of goods and services, for example, when such information is provided in connection with webcasts, white papers or other sponsored downloads. While many customers appreciate the communications, they receive from the third-party providers of goods and services to whom we provide lists of our customers, if you no longer wish to receive messages from individual providers, follow the unsubscribe link and instructions at the bottom of the provider's message or contact the third-party provider directly to be removed from their list.

When you use a co-branded service (a service operated with a partner of 1105 Media) or register or otherwise provide information on a co-branded site, you grant us permission to pass the information collected back to that partner. This may include third party service providers whose services are embedded into and/or appear within the Services. Use of your information by such partners may be subject to their privacy policies as well as ours.

In order to help us sell advertising on the Services and otherwise publicize 1105 Media and its brands, we may share aggregate statistics that describe our online audience. Those statistics are often based on the information you provide when you subscribe, register, or browse the Services and describe, among other things, the demographics of our visitors.

With respect to surveys, in the event that responses are publicly disclosed, users will be notified at the time they take the survey. 1105 Media will disclose only aggregate information regarding its users' responses in surveys to other participants in the survey. Where surveys allow users to submit written comments, and where 1105 Media advises users of the possibility of such disclosure at the time they take the survey, 1105 Media reserves the right to disclose any information provided by users, provided that no User Information identifying a specific user is disclosed. Participation in surveys is solely at your discretion.

We may also disclose User Information that we receive from you and from third party and public sources to third parties whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy (e.g., third party providers of goods and services, marketing and advertising companies and agencies, content publishers and retailers). In addition, we provide information to third parties for OBA as discussed above.

1105 Media and some of our advertisers use third party advertising service companies to serve advertisements and perform related services when you visit the Services. Often, these third-party advertising companies employ cookie and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of website, app and email advertisements and to create a record of interaction with our content that they use in conjunction with their advertising which appears on other sites or applications, or for reporting website traffic, app use, statistics, advertisement data and/or other activities on the Services. We also engage third party providers to assist with the segmentation of this data.

The Service may utilize framing techniques to serve content from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our site. Please be aware that you may be providing your information to these third parties and not to 1105 Media, or in some cases such information may be shared with both 1105 Media and such third parties.

#### 5\. How you can change or control what is collected.

**Updating Your Registration Information.** **  
** Upon request, 1105 Media will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Information. You can also view, correct, delete or change the information collected during user registration at any time at the profile page for that membership, app or website. Please allow five to ten business days for corrections or changes to be publicly displayed or implemented throughout our systems. If you have any trouble accessing, correcting or deleting any of your information, or would like to make a request about whether 1105 Media holds any of your Personal Information, please contact the website directly by clicking on the appropriate link below (which should lead to a "Contact Us" page or support email) or contact us at **[privacy@1105media.com](mailto:privacy@1105media.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)** **(must include "Privacy Policy" in the subject line)** and we will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

**Location Based Services** **.  
**You may opt-out of having your Precise Location Data collected by 1105 Media at any time by editing the appropriate setting on your mobile device (which is usually located in the Settings are of your device) or by emailing us at **[privacy@1105media.com](mailto:privacy@1105media.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy)** **and include "Privacy Policy" in the subject line.**

**Cookies and Pixel Tags** **.  
**You may stop or restrict cookies and pixel tags on your computer or purge cookies from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences. However, if you "turn off," purge, or disable cookies or pixel tags, although you may still use the Services, you may not be able to use all of the features, functions, or services available on the Services. You may download a browser plugin that will help you maintain your opt-out choices by visiting [www.aboutads.info/pmc](http://www.aboutads.info/pmc)

**Unsubscribing from 1105 Media Newsletter and Emails** **.  
**You can opt out or unsubscribe to a newsletter or other email list at any time by following the instructions at the end of the newsletters or emails you receive or by **[Clicking Here](https://1105.dragonforms.com/init.do?pk=PP&omedasite=ONE6909_1105pref)** to update your email preferences. Please allow five to ten business days for changes to take effect. On some Services, member service-related communications are an integral part of such Services to which you subscribe and you may continue to receive emails as part of that particular portion of the Services unless you cancel your account, even if you opt out of the newsletters or email list. If you have provided more than one email address to us, you may continue to be contacted unless you request to unsubscribe each email address you have provided

**Postal Communications  
**If you volunteer a postal address you may receive periodic mailings to relate information about new products, services, and/or upcoming events. We may also provide this information to other carefully selected outside companies for promotional purposes. If you do not wish to receive mailings from us or other companies, please let us know by clicking on the statement below and following the steps provided, calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address.

**I do not wish to receive any mailings from 1105 Media Inc. or other companies.**

It will take up to 3 months to process your do-not-mail request. Please note that you may receive additional communications from us or other companies after submitting your request if your postal address was selected from our database just prior to receiving and processing your request.

**Telephone Communications  
**If you volunteer a telephone number you may receive periodic telephone calls about new products, services, and/or upcoming events. We may also provide this information to carefully selected outside companies for promotional purposes. If you do not wish to receive telephone calls from us or other companies, please let us know by clicking on the statement below and following the steps provided, calling us at the above telephone number, or writing to us at the above address.

**I do not wish to receive any telephone calls from 1105 Media Inc. or other companies.**

**Push Notifications** **.  
**We send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running. If you no longer wish to receive these types of communications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information.

**California Residents** **.  
**In accordance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act, we may collect Personal Information about your online activities when you use the Services. While we give our users many avenues to opt out of providing Personal Information, we do not respond to Web browsers' "do not track" signals. If you wish for us to refrain from gathering your Personal Information, please see our section on **How to Change or Control What Is Collected**. California's "Shine the Light" law, Civil Code Section 1798.83, permits our users who are California residents to periodically request and obtain certain information about any Personal Information disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and wish to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to:

_1105 Media  
6300 Canoga Ave., Suite 1150   
Woodland Hills, CA, 91367  
Attn: Data Services Department_

#### 6\. Information for users located outside the U.S.

The Services operate and are hosted in the United States and, depending on your country of residence, the submission of personally identifiable information to the Services may involve some transfer of User Information to the United States. You understand and consent to having any User Information you provide transferred to and processed in the United States. You should be aware that privacy laws in the United States may not provide protections equivalent to those of your country of residence.

Please note that we may use data collected by a third party operator/licensee of localized versions or editions of Services.

1105 Media privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy comply with the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (" **APEC** ") Cross Border Privacy Rules System. To learn more about this program, please click **[here](http://www.apec.org/Groups/Committee-on-Trade-and-Investment/~/media/Files/Groups/ECSG/CBPR/CBPR-PoliciesRulesGuidelines.ashx)**.

#### 7\. How this Privacy Policy can change.

Some or all User Information maintained by 1105 Media may be subject to transfer to another company in the event of a change of ownership of 1105 Media or sale of any part of 1105 Media. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our websites in the event of any change in ownership along with a material change of the uses of your Personal Information.

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and all changes will be effective at the time we post them. If we believe there is a significant change to this Privacy Policy or our data collection and use practices, we will indicate on our websites that our Privacy Policy has changed prior to the change becoming effective. The then-posted version of the Privacy Policy supersedes all prior versions. Your continued access to or use of any of the Services shall be deemed your acceptance of the Privacy Policy.

**We urge you to come back to this web page and review this Privacy Policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you.**

#### 8\. Other useful information regarding your privacy.

**Security** **.**  
We believe we use reasonable precautions to keep the Personal Information you disclose to the Services secure. However, we cannot guarantee there will not be a breach, and we are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of any third parties. In certain instances, we may use Secure Sockets Layer encryption and/or transfer certain User Information in a non-human readable format to provide protection. You are ultimately responsible for the security of your email address and password.

**Children**.  
The Services are not intended for use by children, especially those under 13. No one under age 13 should provide any Personal Information or use our public discussion areas, forums or chats. Minors under the age of 18 are prohibited from making purchases on the Service or obtaining coupons or codes from the Services to purchase goods or services on third party websites. If, notwithstanding these prohibitions, your children disclose information about themselves in our public discussion areas, consequences may occur that are not intended for children (for example, they may receive unsolicited messages from other parties). If it is discovered that we have collected Personal Information from someone under 13, we will delete that information immediately.

**Data Retention** **.**  
The time period for which we keep information varies according to the information's use. In some cases, there are legal requirements to keep data for a minimum period. Unless there is a specific legal requirement for us to keep the information, we plan to retain it for no longer than is necessary to fulfill a legitimate business need.

**Links to Other Sites.**   
The Services contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. You should consult the privacy policy of these other sites to learn how your privacy is protected.

#### 9.Enforcement

**Complaints.**  
1105 Media is committed to resolving complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. If you believe that 1105 Media has not complied with this Privacy Policy, or if you have any other complaint with regard to collection, use or disclosure of information by 1105 Media, please contact [privacy@1105media.com](mailto:privacy@1105media.com) or send your complaint by mail to the following address. Residents of the European Union should submit any such privacy complaints to [privacy@1105media.com](mailto:privacy@1105media.com).

**1105 Media, Inc.**  
6300 Canoga Ave., Suite 1150  
Woodland Hills, CA 91367  
Attention: Data Services  
Fax: (818) 936-0267  
Phone: (866) 410-1321  
Email: [Privacy@1105media.com](mailto:Privacy@1105media.com)
